

CONTACT ME



Address Aarhus C, Denmark



Phone 93 10 74 50



Web Alq@email.dk www.andylq.com

FOLLOW ME

LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/andylq

ABOUT ME

I am 23 years old and Aarhus C based.

My mothertongue is **Danish** and i speak **English** fluently.

I am currently studying **Web development** at the Business Academy Aarhus finishing december 2020.

Visit my website for more info www.andylq.com

Feel free to contact me **anytime**, email or phone.
I have alot of time at the moment because of Covid-19.

ANDY LE QUACH

WEB DEVELOPER

I am a confident student with experience in management and teamwork. In working environments i am savy and function well in stressful situations.

I am ready for anything in web development, i am still new to the game.

Because of past experience, i know the importance of effective communication and work well in teams.

Lastly i am very flexible and good at adapting my priorities.



EXPERIENCE

Jan 2018 - April 2018 DigitalGuest

MULTIMEDIA INTERN

At my internship at DigitalGuest i mainly worked with multimedia. I had alot of focus of the website of the company, but also solved other tasks including graphic design, and a bit of JavaScipt code for the developer team

2013 - 2018 McDonald's Tilst

SHIFT MANAGER

My time working at McDonald's taught me alot about working in and managing big teams, leadership, optimizing and what a good working environment should look like.



EDUCATION

2019 - 2020 Business Academy Aarhus

BACHELOR IN WEB DEVELOPMENT

As a top-op on the AP degree in Multimedia design , i am currently getting a Bachelor degree in Web development. Here we are taught web design, web publishing, web programming, database management, user testing, etc.

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018 Humber College

DIGITAL COMMUNICATIONS

This was a part of the Multimedia design programme where i choose to go abroad to Toronto, Canada. Here i was put in the digital communication programme, which was the equivalent to Multimedia design

2017 - 2019 Business Academy Aarhus

AP DEGREE, MULTIMEDIA DESIGN

At the Multimedia design program, we learned about HTML, CSS and JavaScript, together with content creation, web design, UX, SoMe strategies, User testing, prototyping and SEO.